Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-642. Wages
    - Lexington Union Station, Lexington, Kentucky. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 35)
    - Lexington Union Station, Lexington, Kentucky. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-645. Wages
    - Kewaunee, Green Bay and Western Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 37)
    - Kewaunee, Green Bay and Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 582, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 408-646. Wages
    - New Jersey, Indiana and Illinois Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 582, Folder 39)
    - New Jersey, Indiana and Illinois Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 582, Folder 40)
    - New Jersey, Indiana and Illinois Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 582, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 408-648. Wages
    - Western Warehousing Company, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania Division. General, 1952-1956 (Box 583, Folder 1)
    - Western Warehousing Company, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania Division. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 2)
    - Western Warehousing Company, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania Division. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 3)
    - Western Warehousing Company, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania Division. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-653. Wages
    - Los Angeles Junction Railway, Los Angeles, California. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 5)
    - Los Angeles Junction Railway, Los Angeles, California. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 583, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-656. Wages
    - Northern Alberta Railways. General, 1950 (Box 583, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-657. Wages
    - Lakefront Dock and Railroad Terminal Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 8)
    - Lakefront Dock and Railroad Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 9)
    - Lakefront Dock and Railroad Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 408-660. Wages
    - Allied Aviation Service Company of Massachusetts, Inc. General, 1950 (Box 583, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-661. Wages
    - Arkansas and Louisiana Missouri Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 12)
    - Arkansas and Louisiana Missouri Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-664. Wages
    - Walla Walla Valley Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 14)
    - Walla Walla Valley Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 15)
    - Walla Walla Valley Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 583, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-668. Wages
    - Atlantic and Danville Railway Company. Norfolk, Franklin and Danville Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 17)
    - Atlantic and Danville Railway Company. Norfolk, Franklin and Danville Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 18)
    - Atlantic and Danville Railway Company. Norfolk, Franklin and Danville Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-671. Wages
    - Waukegan North Chicago Transit Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 583, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-672. Wages
    - Benwood and Wheeling Connecting Railway, Wheeling, West Virginia. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 583, Folder 21)
    - Benwood and Wheeling Connecting Railway, Wheeling, West Virginia. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 583, Folder 22)
    - New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal, New Orleans, Louisiana. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-675. Wages
    - New Orleans Union Passenger Terminal, New Orleans, Louisiana. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 583, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-676. Wages
    - E.W. Coslett and Sons. General, 1946-1959 (Box 583, Folder 25)
    - E.W. Coslett and Sons. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 583, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-678. Wages
    - Central Greyhound Lines. Chicago Greyhound Terminal, Inc. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-679. Wages
    - Caribbean Atlantic Airlines, Inc. Mediation Case No. A-6499, 1961-1962 (Box 583, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-682. Wages
    - Los Angeles Metropolitan Transit Authority, Los Angeles, California. Metropolitan Coach Lines, Inc. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-683. Wages
    - Abilene and Southern Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 30)
    - Abilene and Southern Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-686. Wages
    - Baines, N.H., Concession Stand. Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 583, Folder 32)
    - Baines, N.H., Concession Stand. Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 583, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-687. Wages
    - Bauxite and Northern Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 408-689. Wages
    - Western Maryland Warehouse Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 408-694. Wages
    - Chicago Heights Terminal Transfer Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 36)
    - Chicago Heights Terminal Transfer Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 37)
    - Chicago Heights Terminal Transfer Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 408-695. Wages
    - Live Oak, Perry and Gulf and South Georgia Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7063, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 39)
    - Live Oak, Perry and Gulf and South Georgia Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 583, Folder 40)
    - Live Oak, Perry and Gulf and South Georgia Railway Company. Mediation Case No. A-5120, 1956 (Box 583, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 408-711. Wages
    - New York Connecting Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 42)
    - New York Connecting Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 408-712. Wages
    - Herman, R.B., Company. Suburban Station Building Corporation. McCloskey Enterprises, Inc. General, 1957-1966 (Box 583, Folder 44)
    - Herman, R.B., Company. Suburban Station Building Corporation. McCloskey Enterprises, Inc. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 583, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 408-713. Wages
    - Brownsville and Matamoros Bridge Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 408-715. Wages
    - Baker Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 583, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 408-716. Wages
    - Southern Pacific Building Company. General, 1957-1961 (Box 583, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 408-719. Wages
    - Union Pacific Hospital Association. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1958 (Box 583, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 408-723. Wages
    - East Coast Hospital Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 408-735. Wages
    - Western Pacific Medical Department. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1964 (Box 583, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 408-736. Wages
    - Southern Pacific Hospital Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 583, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 408-740. Wages
    - Trans-Caribbean Airways. Mediation Case No. A-6169, 1960 (Box 583, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 408-756. Wages
    - Bush Terminal Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 408-758. Wages
    - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, International Office. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 408-759. Wages
    - Transportation Hospital Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 583, Folder 56)